Are you working late tonight?
你今晚加班吗?
Excuse me. Yes? Trish.
对不起.什么事?Trish.
Constanza Fuentes?
Are you sure? OK.
你确定吗?好的.
Hobart... Hello, Constanza...
Hobart...喂,Constanza...
How are you?
你好吗?
Fine, thank you.
很好,谢谢.
How can I help you?
我能为你做什么吗?
Uh huh...Yes...Excuse me?
Uh huh...是的...什么?
No, I hadn't.
不,我没有.
I...uh...sure.
我...uh...当然.
I'd be happy to consider it.
我很乐意考虑此事.
Lunch on Thursday.
周四一起吃午饭.
Fine.
好的.
See you then.
到时候见.
Constanza Fuentes?
As in Party Chairwoman Fuentes?
做党主席的那位Fuentes?
Well? What did she want?
Well?她有什么事?
She asked me if I had ever thought of running for public office.
她问我是否曾考虑过竞选公职.
Any particular one?
具体什么职位?
Attorney General of the State of Massachusetts.
Massachusetts州首席检察官.
That's right. Phil's retiring.
没错.Phil就要退休了.
What does our boss think about you taking his place?
我们的头儿对你接替他有什么想法?
Constanza said Phil loves the idea.
Constanza说Phil很支持.
What else did she say?
她还说别的什么吗?
Not much.
说的不多.
She said we are doing a great job and I have a lot to offer and they need a candidate.
她说我们公职干得很好,说我可以做许多事,他们需要一个候选人.
So you said you'll think about it.
所以你说你将考虑此事.
Yeah. Am I crazy? Can I do this?
是的.我是不是疯了?我能胜任吗?
If you want to.
如果你想的话就能.
I have to tell Nancy what's going on.
我得跟Nancy谈谈这事.
We can finish this later.
这个我们可以稍后完成.